boltblue.com 2012-12-13

# Ringtones, Mobile Games, Wallpapers, Text Messaging, Boltblue

Boltblue is operated by:

**Boltblue Communications Limited**  
91 Peterborough Road  
London  
SW6 3BU

This privacy policy explains our commitments and your rights concerning your personal information. You should read it carefully.

## What we collect

We may hold personal information relating to you that you have provided to us (such as registration information or product purchase information) or that we have obtained from another source. This information may include your name, gender, age, address, mobile and other telephone numbers, credit information, information on how you use our products and services (such as the type, date, time, location and duration of calls or messages, the numbers you call and how much you spend and information on your browsing activity when visiting our business or consumer websites) and any other information with respect to your use of our products and services.

We create a "cookie" when you first register online. A cookie is a piece of information, like a tag, that is stored on your computer's hard drive. Our cookie stores some basic information about you that helps use manage your communications sessions with us and authenticate you as a registered user. The cookie is updated each time you visit our site. Our cookies do not collect any of the following types of information:

• mobile or other telephone numbers  
• any payment or credit information  
• Internet browsing history or data downloaded to your computer

Although you may disable the cookie collecting function on your web browser, you will not be able to access our web site as a registered user unless cookies are enabled.

## How we protect your personal information

We seek to comply worldwide with the Data Protection Act of 1998 (the "Act") and take all reasonable care to prevent any unauthorised access to your personal data. The main principles of the Act are that processing of personal data must be fair and reasonable and personal data should be secure, accurate and up-to-date. Generally speaking, each time we want to collect personal data we must first tell you the purposes for which we will use the data and then ask for your consent. We can only use your data for the purposes to which you consent. We must also tell you if we will transfer your data to anyone else. The Act allows you to write and ask to see and correct data held about you, though we may charge an administrative fee.

We utilise the latest encryption and firewall technology to safeguard your personal information. If you provide your credit card details to us, this information is stored in secure, offline areas of our system that are not accessible from the Internet.

We require those to whom we transfer personal data to keep your information confidential and to use it only for the express purpose for which it was provided. The persons to whom we may provide your personal information include: our commercial partners who supply necessary services to us in connection with the provision of our products and services to you, credit reference agencies who may share your information with other organisations and who may keep a record of the searches we make in your name, persons involved in the prevention or detection of fraud or crime or the apprehension or prosecution of offenders and persons to whom we may be required to pass your information by law or governmental or regulatory authority. We seek to impose restrictions on contracting parties with the aim of protecting your personal data.

Because Boltblue's services operate internationally, the personal information described above may be transferred to and made available in countries that do not have data protection laws or have laws which provide less protection than the European rules. In addition, our websites or databases may be based on servers located outside the European Union. We require those to whom we transfer your data to protect it and your privacy. In this way, we work to protect personal information transferred to countries that do not have adequate data protection laws, including outside the European Union.

Any third party Internet sites that you can access through our sites are not covered by Boltblue's privacy policy and we accept no responsibility or liability for these sites. We urge you to be careful when you enter any personal information on these sites.

## How we use your personal information

We use personal information for administration and to support, improve and obtain feedback on our products and services and to prevent and detect breaches of network security, unlawful acts or breaches of our contract terms. We may contact you to ask for feedback on the products and services, obtain suggestions for improvements or inform you of any of our new or improved products and services. We may also use personal information to assess which products and services may be of interest to individuals and to personalise the products and services that we provide. We may use personal information such as preferences and demographic information to identify attractive audiences for advertisers. As a result, the types of products and services advertisements that you receive should be more interesting and useful to you. In such cases, while we may contact you with third party offers, we do not disclose your personal information (including your mobile phone number) to third parties. Of course, you have a right to ask us at any time not to contact you by way of direct marketing. Our general principle is not to sell personal data about our customers or users to other persons.

Boltblue and your bank or credit card issuer may use the information supplied by you to administer and support our services and products Service and to prevent fraud and abuse. You agree to allow us to work with your bank or credit card issuer solely for these purposes.

Our website uses ad servers (such as Adlink, DoubleClick and Valueclick) to serve advertisements that appear on the pages of our website. These ad servers may use cookies in the process of serving advertisements, but they will not collect any personally identifiable information about you. For more information about the ad servers, cookies and how to "opt out", please see their privacy statements: Adlink, [DoubleClick](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy) and [Valueclick](http://www.valueclick.com/).

We would like to keep you informed by fax, post, email or free messages of other Boltblue products and services. However, if you do not wish to be kept so informed you can indicate this by sending an email to [privacy@boltbluecorp.com](mailto:privacy@boltbluecorp.com) at any time.

The law allows you to see and correct data held about you. If you have any questions about the Boltblue's data protection policy you should contact [privacy@boltbluecorp.com](mailto:privacy@boltbluecorp.com).
